[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Ouija, referring to a talking board, is derived from what?", "correct_answer": "The French oui for yes, and the German ja for yes", "incorrect_answers": ["A board created by Nazis for Hitler meaning Holy Grail", "An Ancient Egyptian word meaning good luck", "Ancient Hebrew meaning spirit talker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many box turtle species are there in North America?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "9", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To build the 747, The Boeing Co. needed to design and construct a large number of tools.  Approximately how many?", "correct_answer": "270 000", "incorrect_answers": ["170 000", "1 800", "45 000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island was originally called Van Diemens Land in honor of Anthony van Diemen.", "correct_answer": "Tasmania", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Indonesia", "New Zealand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the normal body temperature of a healthy platypus?", "correct_answer": "About 32\u00b0C", "incorrect_answers": ["Around 22\u00b0C", "Around 28\u00b0C", "Between 35\u00b0C and 37\u00b0C"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common American nickname for briefs, a type of Y-shaped underwear?", "correct_answer": "Tighty whities", "incorrect_answers": ["Band brands", "People pants", "Cotton cups"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the properties it exhibits, light is defined as what?", "correct_answer": "Both wave and particles", "incorrect_answers": ["Electromagnetic wave", "Living organism", "Group of particles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following happens three days after the moment of death?", "correct_answer": "The body starts to swell", "incorrect_answers": ["The body starts to shrink", "The body starts to emit smell", "The nails are so loose that they can be pulled off"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is used for the enigmatic bovid mammal Kting Voar, which is believed to populate Cambodia and Vietnam in Asia?", "correct_answer": "Snake-eating Cow", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizard-eating Goat", "All of these", "Frog-chewing Sheep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these mountains is highest?", "correct_answer": "Mount McKinley", "incorrect_answers": ["Puncak Jaya", "Mount Elbrus", "Mount Kilimanjaro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used to refer to the young of the kangaroo?", "correct_answer": "Joey", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary", "Jack", "Wally"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the traditional Brazilian dish called Moqueca?", "correct_answer": "Stew", "incorrect_answers": ["Dessert", "Drink", "Salad"]}]